

Divya Vaghasiya Magento Developer

Junagadh

☑ divya.vaghasiya1997@gmail.com

& +91 99043 66701

SOCIAL

in @divya-vaghasiya

@divya-vaghasiya

PROFILE

I have been in this development field for quite a long time 3+ years, and I have worked on Magento 2.x standards/Custom extention development and paid extention customization. I can handle the complete development process which includes UI designing, Development, Rigorous Testing and long term maintenance.

EDUCATION

Bachlor Of Engineering

BH Gardi - Rajkot

2014 - 2018

HSC

GPS high school

2012 - 2014

SSC

GPS high school

2011 - 2012

SKILLS

- phpHTML
- Magento2CSS
- MySQL jQuery

EXPERIENCE

Magento2 Developer

-From 2021 to till today | Design N Buy

- Developed a reseller module that allow you to create mutliple websites without any storeview concept. A custom commission system for products was also implemented in that.
- Improved SEO by optimizing URLs, titles, descriptions and alt tags on all images in the store
- Implemented Google Analytics tracking code and created goals based on traffic sources and sales conversions
- Developed and maintained websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Integrated email verification with the registration process for new customers
- Conducted technical analysis of existing business requirements.
- Resolved software bugs and prepared cost and time estimates.
- Maintained some stores, implemented new functionality, customized and maintained existing extensions. Had a direct communication with the customer. Made integration with third-party services and upgraded Magento version and applied patches.

Magento2, Wordpress and core PHP

- -From 2019 to 2021 | The Launch Engine
- Build websites using WordPress.
- Prepare website proposals to present to clients.
- Customize themes and plugins to meet clients' requirements.
- Manage a user guide to help clients understand site features and management of website to increase visitor satisfaction.

Core PHP

- -From 2018 to 2019 | Universal Stream Solution
- Created and used a prototype library for AJAX development.
- Worked on frontend and backend validation.
- Created one page site with form submit using HTML, CSS, BootStrap, JavaScript and PHP.
- Developed API in Codignitor.

LANGUAGES

• English • Hindi • Gujarati

INTERESTS

∩ ⊕ □ □
Music Shopping Reading Movie